freshpreserving.com 2019-04-29

# Privacy Policy

BY USING OR ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACKNOWLEDGMENT AND ASSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. PLEASE READ THIS POLICY CAREFULLY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE.

This policy is intended to help you understand how Newell Brands Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "Newell Brands," "we" or "us") collect, use and safeguard the information you provide on this website. This policy covers this website and all Newell Brands websites except where otherwise indicated. Some Newell Brands websites may have policies that supplement this policy. We encourage you to read this policy and any supplemental policies on Newell Brands websites. In the event of any conflict between this policy and terms set forth in a supplemental policy, the latter will apply to the website on which such supplemental policy is posted.

## **Collection of Personal Information**

If you browse any Newell Brands website, you may generally do so anonymously without providing any personal information. However, there are cases in which we may ask you for personal data. For example, we will occasionally conduct on-line surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors. In addition, we may request personal information when you register to receive additional information regarding our products and services, download software, sign up for a newsletter or send us a question. In such cases, the personal information we request will typically consist of: your title, first and last name, mailing address and email address, as well as certain billing and credit card information for purposes of effecting payments. Additionally, we may provide you with the option of submitting information such as your birthday, anniversary date, information regarding the size and composition of your household and your preferred retailers, all of which are intended to enhance your experience, and inform you, of our product and service offerings Even if you choose not to give information we request, you can still visit most of the Newell Brands website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services.

## **Newell Brands Mailings/Marketing Communications**

If you provide us with personal information, and choose to join a particular company's e-mail list, we will place you on that company's list to receive e-mail regarding product/service updates, special offers, important issues and new products and services from that company as well as other subsidiaries and affiliates of Newell Brands. The personal information that you provide to that particular company will be shared internally with other subsidiaries and affiliates of Newell Brands. If you do not wish to receive e-mail updates or other marketing communications from that particular company or other Newell Brands subsidiariesand affiliates, please contact us at the opt-out e-mail address specified below. 

## **Sharing and Use of Personal Information**

Personal information provided to us may be used for marketing and promotional purposes only by Newell Brands. Except as described in this policy, Newell Brands does not rent, sell or otherwise distribute to third parties, your personal information entered on this site without your consent, unless required by law or as disclosed to you when the information is collected. If you do provide us with consent to share your information with other third party companies, we may share your information with third party companies who offer products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may then contact you directly with product or sample offers, personalized offers and information, or to ask for your feedback on products and programs that they think may be of interest to you.

We may share your personal information with our third party service providers on a need-to-know basis. We engage third party service providers to perform certain services on our behalf. In order to perform those services, the service providers may need to know your personal information. We require that they protect this information and only use it to perform services on our behalf. For example, we may use outside shipping companies, credit card processing companies, resellers, distributors and content providers.

Additionally, we may share statistical, anonymized or aggregated non-personal information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. This data is used to customize Newell Brands website content and advertising to deliver a better experience to our users.

## **Special Cases**

Newell Brands reserves the right to disclose user information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Newell Brands website users or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information without notice to you in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to respond to an emergency situation. We also may disclose personal information as part of a merger or acquisition.

## **Transfer of Personal Information**

Depending on the country in which you are located, your personal information may be transferred to another country for data storage and processing. When we transfer personal information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to transfer the information in compliance with all applicable data protection laws.

## **Cookies and IP Tracking**

This site may use cookies for site administration purposes. If for any reason you wish to not take advantage of cookies, you may have your browser not accept them, although this may disable or render unusable some of the features of the Newell Brands website.

This website also may detect and use your IP address or domain name for internal traffic monitoring and capacity purposes or to otherwise administer our website. No personal information is obtained; rather, just the patterns of usage of our various users may be tracked to provide you with improved service and content based on aggregate or statistical reviews of user site traffic patterns.

## **Other Analytic Tools**

We may use Google Analytics and other analytic tools to gather aggregate, non-identifiable information. Such tools enable us to gather information such as what pages people visit, which products they look at, what device they use and where they are located. Additionally, we currently use CRM tools as part of our CRM program, which allows us to register users on our website and better understand what content they are browsing and which products are of interest to them for ranking and marketing purposes. 

## **Do-Not-Track**

Currently, (i) other parties (e.g. third-party advertising networks and analytics providers) may not collect personal information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our website or services, and (ii) we do not respond to, or take any specific action in connection with the receipt of, Do-Not-Track signals or other similar mechanisms regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services.

## **Policies for Children**

Generally, our websites are not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect information from children under such age; moreover, Newell Brands encourages parents and guardians to monitor and participate in their children's online activities. However, certain of our websites may be directed to such children and, in such cases, the privacy policy for such website will state this, and we shall use commercially reasonable efforts to comply with all applicable laws intended to protect such children, including the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Unless you are viewing a website directed specifically to children, no information should be submitted to this site by users under 13 years of age, and users under 13 years of age are not allowed to register for newsletters, clubs or activities. In addition, users under 18 years of age are not allowed to make purchases or participate in contests, except for those specifically directed to children. Where appropriate, Newell Brands may ask you to indicate your age to verify compliance with these policies.

## **Linked Sites**

Please be advised that this website may contain links to third party websites. The linked sites are not under the control of Newell Brands, and we are not responsible for the content, or privacy practices or other activities of any linked site or any link on a linked site.

## **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Newell Brands reserves the right to change or update this policy, or any other policy or practice, at any time. We will provide individuals who have submitted personal information to us with reasonable notice of material changes to this website. Additionally, you are encouraged from time to time to review any updated versions of this policy, as indicated by the effective date of this policy set forth below. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Newell Brands site. Your use of this website after such changes or updates have been posted signifies your acceptance of the changed terms.

## **Changes to your Personal Information**

In case you have questions about this policy or our related practices, or wish to review, update or delete personal information about yourself submitted to or collected by us, we will endeavor to answer such questions, facilitate such review and correct, update or remove the personal data in question, as requested. In such case, please contact us via the contact points specified below:

## **Ethics and Compliance Team**

Newell Brands Inc.  
6655 Peachtree Dunwoody Road  
Atlanta, Georgia 30328  

Additionally, if you would like your e-mail address removed from our database, please send an e-mail to [optout@newellco.com](mailto:optout@newellco.com), and type the word "Remove" in the subject line. 

Please note that questions about our products and services should not be directed to privacy@newellco.com or [optout@newellco.com](mailto:optout@newellco.com) and will not receive a reply. 

Effective Date: This policy is effective as of December 16, 2016.
